[
    {
        "id":1,
        "question":"Ephebiphobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["teenagers or adolescents", "loud music", "babies","people kissing"],
        "correct_answer":"teenagers or adolescents"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"Alektorophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["chickens or hens", "selectors", "election", "bulls"],
        "correct_answer":"chickens or hens"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"Amathophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["dust", "knots", "math", "tangled hair"],
        "correct_answer":"dust"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["long words", "slick surfaces", "hippos", "big boulders"],
        "correct_answer":"long words"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"Globophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["balloons", "ball gowns", "licking","world maps"],
        "correct_answer":"balloons"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"Phobophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["fear itself", "photosynthesis", "green plants", "black couches"],
        "correct_answer":"fear itself"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"Nomophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["being without a smartphone", "even numbers", "gamers out in public", "worms in a jar"],
        "correct_answer":"being without a smartphone"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question":"Panophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["everything", "pan pizza", "pandemics", "pantomime"],
        "correct_answer":"everything"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question":"Athazagoraphobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["forgetting or being forgotten", "antiques", "cardboard boxes", "snow"],
        "correct_answer":"forgetting or being forgotten"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"Vestiphobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["clothing", "hall ways", "fresh smells", "sliced tomatoes"],
        "correct_answer":"clothing"
    },
    {
        "id":11,
        "question":"Cibophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["food", "insects", "oddly shaped objects", "star fish"],
        "correct_answer":"food"
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "question":"Ergophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["work", "ergonomic chairs", "mouse pads", "screen light from tv"],
        "correct_answer":"work"
    },
    {
        "id":13,
        "question":"Ablutophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["bathing and cleaning", "horn section in orchestra", "blood", "sounds from horse hooves"],
        "correct_answer":"bathing and cleaning"
    },
    {
        "id":14,
        "question":"Dextrophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["having objects to your right", "ornaments on the tree", "dextrose sugars", "dirt under the shoes"],
        "correct_answer":"having objects to your right"
    },
    {
        "id":15,
        "question":"Siderophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["stars", "consideration", "web sites", "tractors"],
        "correct_answer":"stars"
    },
    {
        "id":16,
        "question":"Plutophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["money", "small planets", "cartoon characters", "snow men"],
        "correct_answer":"money"
    },
    {
        "id":17,
        "question":"Ideophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["reason or ideas", "juniper tree", "caves", "coffee grounds"],
        "correct_answer":"reason or ideas"
    },
    {
        "id":18,
        "question":"Geliophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["laughter", "gelato", "jello", "helium voices"],
        "correct_answer":"laughter"
    },
    {
        "id":19,
        "question":"Omphalophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["belly buttons", "color blue", "litt candles", "wooden desks"],
        "correct_answer":"belly buttons"
    },
    {
        "id":20,
        "question":"Xanthophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["the color yellow", "xylophone", "hemorrhoids", "big things"],
        "correct_answer":"the color yellow"
    },
    {
        "id":21,
        "question":"Eleutherophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["freedom", "elevation", "truth", "mischievious elfs"],
        "correct_answer":"freedom"
    },
    {
        "id":22,
        "question":"Chaetophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["hair", "cheetahs", "cheaters", "pointy shoes"],
        "correct_answer":"hair"
    },
    {
        "id":23,
        "question":"Kathisophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["sitting down", "people named Kathrine", "cats", "catheters"],
        "correct_answer":"sitting down"
    },
    {
        "id":24,
        "question":"Kinemortophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["zombies", "cinemas", "China and all things chinese", "sudden movements"],
        "correct_answer":"zombies"
    },
    {
        "id":25,
        "question":"Linonophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["string", "bed linens", "glue", "coat liners"],
        "correct_answer":"string"
    },
    {
        "id":26,
        "question":"Ostraconophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["shellfish", "easter", "purple cars", "orange cones"],
        "correct_answer":"shellfish"
    },
    {
        "id":27,
        "question":"Arachibutyrophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["peanut butter sticking to the roof of your mouth", "spiders", "chewing gum", "trees in the forrest"],
        "correct_answer":"peanut butter sticking to the roof of your mouth"
    },
    {
        "id":28,
        "question":"Pogonophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["beards", "sticks", "poledancing", "hairy nuts"],
        "correct_answer":"beards"
    },
    {
        "id":29,
        "question":"Trypophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["a pattern of holes", "typos", "preassure", "typewriter"],
        "correct_answer":"a pattern of holes"
    },
    {
        "id":30,
        "question":"Pteronophobia is the fear of...?",
        "answers":["feathers or being tickled by feathers", "pterodactylus, or other flying lizzards", "nose hair", "scrunched napkins"],
        "correct_answer":"feathers or being tickled by feathers"
    }
]